

I NEED TO create restraints for my game/game engine. Since this is my first, the absolute most important part is finishing it. 
I'll never finish it, being so new to it, if I'm always trying to improve/iterate endlessly on every design choice, or if I'm
adding in every feature that I think "would be cool". I just need a finished, fully realized "first draft", by July 13th, 2018.
That is one month, more than enough time to make a simple endless runner/platformer, or a VERY basic procedual generated platformer.


THIS GAME WILL NO LONGER BE THE GAME I SET OUT TO MAKE! I NEED TO REMEMBER THIS. THIS IS A COMPLETELY DIFFERENT GAME NOW. A MUCH 
SMALLER, MORE CONCISE, AND BASIC GAME. THIS CAN ALSO BE A PROOF-OF-CONCEPT, IF I START GETTING INVESTED IN IT. BUT THE IMPORTANT PART
IS THAT EVEN IF I GET INVESTED, I ABSOLUTELY MUST FIRST FINISH THIS BASIC GAME

Rules so far : (can be changed a SMALL bit, and only if I'm pruning the ideas even smaller)

- 3 enemy types (possibly MAX 4, if it's not too much work)
- One "level", even if it's procedual, or endless runner types (I don't know if I like this; I'm not sure that more levels=much more work, especially on the coding end)
